wdl.org 2003-04-28

# Wilmington Drama League | Community Theater in Wilmington Delaware -- Privacy Policy

|  | 

Protecting your privacy is important to the Wilmington Drama League. We hope the following policy will help you understand how WDL collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide on our website.

**Information Collection**  
If you browse WDL's website, you do so anonymously. We don't collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which parts of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable. The only other information automatically provided to us is the type of computer and operating system you are using. Your browser supplies us with this information. 

At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, such as your email address and postal address, for purposes such as corresponding with us, or reserving tickets online.

**Information Use**  
If you provide us with your email or postal address, or have done so in the past, we will ask you if we can use it to send you updates on the latest WDL news. If you do not want us to contact you, you can choose to "opt out," and WDL will respect your wishes. 

We may also use the information to inform you about upcoming auditions and shows that may be of interest to you. These offers may be based on information you provided in your initial transaction with us or in surveys.

WDL does not share your profile with anyone else outside of WDL without your consent, and no one else can access your information. 

**Declining Email Offers**  
WDL provides customers with an easy means to decline to receive WDL's emails correspondences and other messages. Although most people tell us they appreciate receiving these, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving emails from us by simply replying to the email and informing us of your preferences.

**Data Security**  
WDL is fully committed to data security. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide to us online. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us. In this regard, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data while you are on the Internet. At a minimum, we encourage you to make sure that you are using a secure browser as you surf the Internet. 

**Company Commitment to Privacy**  
WDL's privacy policy is subject to change at any time and without notice. For updates, please return here. 

|
